[
    {
        "front": "とまる",
        "back": "止まる \nto stop",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ていし",
        "back": "停止 \nto stop",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうし",
        "back": "中止 \ncancel",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "あるく",
        "back": "歩く \nto walk",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "とほ",
        "back": "徒歩 \nwalking distance",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんぽ",
        "back": "散歩 \ntake a walk",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんぽ",
        "back": "進歩 \nprogress",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "おだんほどう",
        "back": "おだん歩道 \npedestrian crossing",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "おきる",
        "back": "起きる \nto wake up",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "きしょうじかん",
        "back": "起床時間 \nwalking time",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "はやおき",
        "back": "早起き \nearly riser",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "きぎょうか",
        "back": "起業家 \nentrepreneur",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "もつ",
        "back": "持つ \nto have, to hold",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "じさん",
        "back": "持参 \nto bring along",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "きもち",
        "back": "気持ち \nfeelings",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "もちもの",
        "back": "持ち物 \nbelonging",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しじ（する）",
        "back": "し持（する） \nto support",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "まつ",
        "back": "待つ \nto wait",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "きたい",
        "back": "期待 \nexpectation",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "まちあわせ",
        "back": "待ち合わせ \nto meet",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうたいする",
        "back": "招待する \nto invite",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "まちあいしつ",
        "back": "待合室 \nwaiting room",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かりる",
        "back": "借りる \nto borrow",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃっきん",
        "back": "借金 \nloan",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かす",
        "back": "貸す \nto lend",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちんたい",
        "back": "賃貸 \nrented",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かしや",
        "back": "貸家 \nhouse for rent",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "はじまる",
        "back": "始まる \nto start",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいし",
        "back": "開始 \nstart",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "はじめる",
        "back": "始める \nto start",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しはつ",
        "back": "始発 \nfirst train of the day",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "おわる",
        "back": "終わる \nto  finish, to end",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうでん",
        "back": "終電 \nlast train",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいしゅうかい",
        "back": "最終回 \nlast episode of the series",
        "chapter": "N4 K11"
    }
]